好的，你完成了
All right, you're done.
希望你是用给定的buildUriMatcher函数开始的
Hopefully you started with
the provided buildUriMatcher function.
我们从定义一个新的UriMatcher开始
包含NO_MATCH
We begin with the new UriMatcher
that contains the NO_MATCH
函数因为我们不希望根节点匹配任何东西。
function because we don't want
the root node to match anything.
这是保证代码可读性的典型习惯。
This is typical behavior to make
the code more easy to read.
我正在创建WeatherContract.CONTENT_AUTHORITY.
的快捷方式
I'm making a shortcut to
the WeatherContract.CONTENT_AUTHORITY.
我们的两个底层URI很简单
Our two base URIs are pretty simple.
既然我们已经在WeatherContract中
定义了PATH_WEATHER和PATH_LOCATION
Since we've already defined PATH_WEATHER
and PATH_LOCATION in the contract,
我们只需要把他们分配给对应的整型常量
we can just assign them to their
corresponding integer constants there.
对于PATH_WEATHER，我们将配对
多一个项目
For PATH_WEATHER, we're going to match
a path with just one additional item
WEATHER_WITH_LOCATION在其上面。
我们将配对
WEATHER_WITH_LOCATION we're going
to match a path that just has
附加的一个项目。
one additional item on it.
因为地点可能是一个字符串
我们必须将其与星号匹配
Because location can be a string,
we have to match it with an asterisk.
对于WEATHER_WITH_LOCATION_AND_DATE
我们将与二者都进行匹配
For WEATHER_WITH_LOCATION_AND_DATE
we're going to match two path items.
第一个为我们的地点，一个字符串
The first one of course will
be our location, a string.
但是第二个将会是我们的日期
这将会是一个数字
But the second one will be our date,
which will always be a number.
因为如此我们可以与#配对
Because of that we can
match with the hash sign.